&gt；&gt；steve：那么让我们做另一件事来玩玩。
&gt;&gt; Steve: So let's do one other
thing to play around with.
这就像我们的倒数第二个科学实验就在这片土地上
It'll be like our kind of second to last
science experiment just in the land of
JavaScript浏览器引擎。
the JavaScript browser engine.
我们试试别的。
Let's try something else.
&gt；&gt；Steve：事实证明，如何确定JavaScript的范围可能有一些重要的意义
&gt;&gt; Steve: It turns out that how you scope
your JavaScript can have some important
对事物运行方式的影响。
implications into how things run.
让我们回到我们的好朋友基准测试。
Let’s go back to our
good friend benchmark.
我要做一个小小的测试函数，因为发生了很多事情。
I’m gonna make a little test function just
cuz there’s a lot of stuff happening.
我们会有我们的测试功能，好的，整齐。
We’ll have our test function,
all right, neat.
我们会说就像它会拿到一分一样
We’ll say like it'll take a point and
它会加上它的x和y，我不知道。
it'll add its x and its y, I don't know.
point.x+point.y，
point.x + point.y,
我们会继续，
and we'll go ahead,
做x和y，所以this.x=x。
make that x and y, so this.x = x.
this.y=y，非常酷。
This.y = y, very cool.
然后在这个函数中，我们将创建一个新的点。
And then in this function,
we'll make a new point.
&gt；&gt；Steve：我们将在点上添加x和y。
&gt;&gt; Steve: And we'll add the x and
y at the point.
好的，制作一个对象，它有一个x和y，创建其中一个。
All right, make an object,
it's got an x and y, create one of them.
我们会把它们加在一起。
We'll add them together.
&gt；&gt；steve：所以我们要进去。
&gt;&gt; Steve: So we'll go in here.
我们只是说，每次都调用那个测试函数。
And we'll just say,
call that test function every time.
我不想衡量我做了整件事。
I don't wanna measure me
making the whole thing.
我只是想在练习部分运行它。
I'm just gonna run it
in the exercise part.
不是为了破坏惊喜，但我要把这个数字调低一点。
And not to ruin the surprise, but I'm
gonna turn this number down a little bit.
&gt；&gt；Steve：800毫秒，似乎相当
&gt;&gt; Steve: 800 milliseconds,
that seems like quite
考虑到我有更大的迭代
a bit considering I had that
much larger iteration for
只是加了两个东西，结果是47。
just adding 2 things, and it was 47.
我想这大概会持续8秒钟，
I think this would go for
about eight seconds,
如果我真的听之任之。
if I let it really go for it.
这似乎是不可接受的。
That seems unacceptable.
对我来说很奇怪，对吧？
And it’s like weird to me, right?
这有什么不同？
How is this that much different?
我不知道。
I don’t know.
我量过了。
I’ve measured.
我知道这很糟糕。
I know that it’s bad.
我只是要移动一些代码。
I’m just gonna move some code around.
别管我。
Don’t mind me.
让我们继续把这个放在这里，好吗？
Let's go ahead and
put this up here, right?
我不需要在每次迭代中都定义类。
I don't need to define
the class in every iteration.
&gt；&gt；Steve：9毫秒，[笑]这稍微快了一点。
&gt;&gt; Steve: Nine milliseconds,
[LAUGH] that's a wee bit faster.
好的，现在有人会争辩说，好吧，你在每次运行中都创建了一个类。
Okay, now one would argue, well,
you are creating a class in every run.
我不认为这是让我从9毫秒到800毫秒的原因，对吧？
I don't think that's what got me
from 9 milliseconds to 800, right?
看起来这里可能有别的事情发生。
It seems like there might be
something else going on here.
所以我有些怀疑。
And so I have some suspicions.
所以我要做的就是再试一件事。
So what I'm gonna do is I'm
gonna just try one more thing.
还记得我比较所有这些类型的时候吗？
Remember when I was
comparing all those types?
我想试试另一件事。
I wanna try one other thing.
我要继续我要抓住这一点
I'm gonna go ahead and
I'm gonna grab this point and
把它带回一班。
bring it back to the classes one.
我要在这里做些科学研究。
I'm gonna do some science here.
我已经有了，太好了。
I had it already, that's great.
所以在另一种情况下，我做了一个这样的
So in the other case,
I was making one of these
在测试函数中，另一个我把它放在了一个作用域上。
inside the test function, and
the other one I had it up a scope.
我有相同的点类，我不是一直在重写它。
I had it the same point class,
I wasn't rewriting it all the time.
所以我运行了这段代码，我知道这些都是相同的类型。
So I've run this code,
I know that these are the same type.
如果我有一个
What if I had a,
&gt；&gt；Steve：我们将返回一个新的点。
&gt;&gt; Steve: We'll return a new point.
&gt；&gt；steve：我们会说做一个重点。
&gt;&gt; Steve: And we'll say make a point.
&gt；&gt；steve：我们会看看他们是否有相同的地图。
&gt;&gt; Steve: And
we'll see if they have the same map.
&gt；&gt；Steve：它们没有，但它们是由相同的基础设施构成的
&gt;&gt; Steve: They don't, but they were made
from the same infrastructure that worked
最后一次对吧？
last time, right?
我们看到了。
We saw it.
我不会失去它，对吧？
I'm not losing it, right?
我们看到，当我上次使用点类时，它们是相同的。
We saw that when I used the point class
last time that they were the same.
现在我在这个函数中做，它们是不同的。
And now I'm doing it inside this
function and they're different.
而且，它要慢得多。
Also, it's way slower.
比如9毫秒对800毫秒
Like 9 milliseconds versus 800.
有猜想吗？
Any guesses?
当我们在函数内部表达观点时，理论上它不是解析。
When we make the point inside of a
function, it's not parsing, theoretically.
我们每一次都在这样做，这是真的。
We are doing it every time, that is true.
但并不是解析造成了很大的不同。
But it's not the parsing
making the big difference.
我们每次都将这个类作为一个不同的原型链，对吧，
We're making this class as a different
prototype chain every time, right,
这意味着从这里出来的每一个点都指向
which means that each one of these
points that come out of here points to
一个不同的原型对象。
a different prototype object.
我们每次都做一个新的点函数，以此类推。
We're making a fresh point function
every time, so on and so forth.
我们可以看到我把代码放在哪里的这个细微的差别
And we can see that this little, tiny
difference in where I've put that code
显然对我的代码有多慢产生了戏剧性的影响。
clearly had dramatic effects
on how slow my code was.
9毫秒，800毫秒，对吧？
9 milliseconds, 800 milliseconds, right?
现在，这是否意味着在今天的午餐期间，我们会检查我们的代码库和
Now, does this mean that during lunch
today we go through our code bases and
每次我在另一个函数中有一个类的时候，我们都在寻找？
we look for every time I've got
a class inside another function?
不，但它会注意到你敞开心扉
No, but it does notice you open up
您的Web应用程序在生产模式下运行时。
your web application while it's
running in production mode.
你晚点去看，你做表演的事情，你就像，哇，
You go later and see, you run
the performance thing, you're like, wow,
这需要很长的时间，对吧？
that's taking a really long time, right?
然后，你开始钻进去。
Then, you begin to spelunk in there.
至少你可以对这些东西是如何工作的有一些假设，所以
And at least you can have some hypotheses
about how this stuff actually works, so
你不是在往墙上扔东西，对吧？
that you're not just throwing
stuff at the wall, right?
我知道如果我在一个函数内部制作东西，它可以有一个不同的链，
I know that if I'm making stuff inside of
a function it can have a different chain,
我知道如果他们通过不同的途径到达同一个物体，
I know if they went through different
paths to get to the same object,
这可能就是问题所在对吧？
that can be the problem, right?
不要推测性地遍历您的代码库，并在任何地方都这样做。
Do not speculatively go through your
code base and do this everywhere.
但我想，这个加载时间太长了。
But I'm like,
this is taking too long to load.
或者就像我在那里看到的红色小三角形。
Or like I see the little
red triangle there.
或者我看到我正沿着这条线钉住CPU或其他什么东西。
Or I see that I'm pegging the CPU or
something along those lines.
现在，是的，我们对这里发生的事情有一些假设，对吗？
Now, yes, we have some hypotheses
on what's happening here, right?
我们甚至还没有接触到浏览器的土地，
We haven't even touched
the browser land yet,
这可能会有一大堆其他的含义。
which can have a whole bunch
of other implications.
但是我们知道并不是所有的JavaScript都是平等的。
But we do know that not all
JavaScript is created equal.
而且我们知道我们的代码是如何构造的，可能会有一些非常戏剧性的东西
And we know that how our code is
structured can have some pretty dramatic
对此的影响。
impacts on that.
我们现在再看一件，涡扇对你做的一件事。
We're gonna look at one more now,
one more thing that turbofan does to you.
好消息是它就像，嘿，它做这件事
And the good news is it's like,
hey, it does this thing for
我和它只是工作的大部分时间，一切都很好，对吗？
me and it just works out most of
the time and everything is great, right?
没有行动项目给你，这是一个很大的解脱之后，
There's no action item for you,
which is big relief after,
我必须担心作用域和我的对象是如何制作的以及诸如此类的事情。
I have to worry about scoping and how my
objects are made and all that kinda stuff.
所以下一个会更有趣。
So this next one'll be
a little bit more fun.
当我们谈论JavaScript编译器时，有趣是一个很强的词。
Fun is a strong word when we're
talking about JavaScript compilers.
所以，是的，但是上一节的要点是，涡扇能够
So, yeah, but the takeaways from
the previous section, turbofan is able to
如果传递一致的值，则以实质性的方式优化代码。
optimize your code in substantial ways
if you pass it consistent values.
那么这对我们来说到底意味着什么呢？
So what does that really mean for us?
如果你可以有一个创建对象的函数，而不是
If you can have a function that
creates the object, rather
比你每次手工做的都要好，如果你总是做一个对象的字面意思，
than you doing it by hand every time,
if you're always making a object literal,
是的，您可以键入花括号和属性，对吗？
yes, you could type the curly braces and
the properties, right?
但是如果你知道如果你使用的很多，它可能是有意义的，使一个函数
But if you know if you're using a lot, it
might make sense to make a function that
为您提供了一个一致的对象，每次都是以相同的方式创建的。
gives you a consistent object that
was created the same way every time.
那样的话，你就不必去想这件事了。
And that way,
you don't have to think about this.
你每时每刻都在想我们刚刚谈到的事情，
Every moment you're thinking about all
the stuff that we just kinda talked about,
就像您可能需要在架构中进行一些更改
it's like you probably have some changes
you need to make in the architecture
你的代码。
of your code.
并且尽量不要在事后修改它们。
And try not to modify them after the fact.
也许以同样的方式创建一个新对象是有意义的。
Maybe it makes sense to make a new
object that gets created the same way.
因为这样做的所有其他物体都会有相同的地图。
Cuz that will have the same map as
all the other objects made that way.
但可能真正容易做到这一点的方法是我们都很高兴
But probably the real easy way to do
this is we all get really happy about
打字稿或流程，就像，是的，我要去做。
TypeScript or Flow and like,
yeah, I'm gonna do it.
然后我必须打字，我不懂打字稿或流程，
And then I have to make a type and
I don't understand TypeScript or Flow and
我对自己说，你知道吗？
I say to myself, you know what?
我只是用JavaScript写这个。
I'm just writing this in JavaScript.
对我来说不值得，[笑]对吗？
It's not worth it for me, [LAUGH] right?
这些系统具有一定的优点，可以避免运行时错误和
There are certain advantages that these
systems above avoiding runtime errors and
诸如此类的事情，有一些优化程序可以做好准备的事情
stuff like that, there are things to
do that the optimizer can get ready for
如果你遵循这个道德准则，一直都有相同的类型，对吗？
if you follow this code of ethics by
having the same types all the time, right?
所以这里的大多数答案要么是测量，然后看看发生了什么，
So most of the answers here are either
measure and see what's happening and,
希望你现在能更好地做出假设。
hopefully, you're a little bit
better at making hypotheses now.
或者，b，在一天结束的时候我要说的是，
Or, b, the point I'm gonna end
with at the end of the day is,
如果我们可以让工具为我们做这些事情，那就太好了，对吧？
be great if we could just have
tools do this stuff for us, right?
这才是最终正确的答案。
That is ultimately the right answer.